얘들아! 멋진 소식이 있어!
맞춰봐!
Guys! Guys! I've got great
news. Guess what.
- 모니카가 임신했구나!
- 정말?
- Monica's pregnant!
- Really?
못들은 걸로 해
Let's get past the moment.
- 무슨 소식인데?
- 고마워
- What's your news?
- Thank you.
나 광고회사에 취직됐어!
I got a job in advertising.
- 와!
- 정말? 축하해!
Honey, that's incredible!
잘됐다!
월급이 얼마야?
Gosh, what's the pay like?
뭘 그렇게 쳐다봐?
Oh, come on, people.
누가 제일 많이 버는지 알아야
If I don't know who makes the most..
누굴 제일 좋아할지 정하지
안녕, 조이?
how do I know who
I like the most? Hi, Joey.
사실 무급직이야
인턴사원이거든
It pays nothing. It's an internship.
멋지다! 우리 인생의 나날들에도
인턴이 나와!
We have interns at Days of Our Lives.
그래, 그 인턴이랑 같은거야
너랑 사귀지 않는다는 것만 빼고
Right. So it'll be the same,
except less sex with you.
어떤 일을 하는데?
What do you think they'll
have you do there?
교육 프로그램인데
끝나면 몇명을 정식고용한대
It's a training program, but they
hire the people they like.
- 잘됐다!
- 짜증나는 일 많을거야
- That's great!
- There's gonna be some grunt work..
잡일도 많을거구 다 큰 남자가
커피 심부름을 하다니 쪽팔리잖아
which will stink. A grown man
getting people coffee is humiliating.
쪽팔리면서도
고귀한 일이지
Humiliating and noble.
고마워요
Thank you.
나도 지금 하는일 아니었다면
You know, if I didn't
already have a job..
광고 쪽에서 잘 나갔을텐데
I would've been good in advertising.
또 "갓 밀크?" 광고
오빠가 먼저 썼다구 우기려고?
Ross, you did not come up with:
"Got Milk?"
정말 내가 먼저 썼어!
Yes, I did! I did!
적어놨어야 하는건데!
I should've written it down.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'피비의 어두운 과거'
챈들러는? 첫 출근하는 날
격려인사 하려고 왔는데
Where's Chandler? I want to wish
him good luck on his first day.
또 베이컨 냄새도 구수하고
And I smelled bacon.
- 출근했어
- 누가?
- He just left.
- Who did?
조이! 그 여자가 전화했어!
Joey, you're never gonna
believe it! She called!
- 정말?
- 네가 됐대!
- She did?
- You got it!
- 내가 됐대?
- 무슨 말이야?
- I did?
- What is she talking about?
뭔지 몰라도
신나는 일 같잖아!
I don't know, but it sounds great!
매니저한테서 전화 왔어!
너 그 오디션 받게 됐대!
Your agent called.
You got that audition!
- 레너드 헤이스 연극?
- 그래!
- With Leonard Hayes?
- Yes!
와, 신난다!
브로드웨이 연극이거든!
Oh, my God, that is great!
It's for a play on Broadway.
진짜 극장에서 하는거야!
지난번처럼 식품점 지하가 아니고!
And in a real theater. Not that little
one underneath the deli like last time.
- 좋은 작품이야?
- 그럴거야!
- Is it a good play?
- It must be.
읽어봤는데
하나도 이해 못하겠더라고!
I read it and didn't
understand a single word!
그리고 레너드 헤이스도
그 연극에 출연해!
- Leonard Hayes is starring in it.
- Yeah, and directing.
연출도 하고!
그사람 맥베스에서
정말 멋있었는데!
He was so good in
that movie of Macbeth.
- 네가 그 영화를 봤어?
- 아니, 예고편만 봤어
- You saw that?
- No, but I saw the previews.
잭애스 보러갔는데
그거 예고편 보여주더라
They played it right before Jackass.
- 맞아, 그사람 진짜 연기 잘해
- 맞아
- He's done some amazing work.
- Oh, yeah.
그 휴대폰 광고에서
너무 멋있잖아!
I loved him in those phone commercials.
원숭이가 큰 고무휴대폰으로
그남자 때렸을때 말야!
When the monkey hits him in the face
with the giant rubber phone..
그 원숭이도 오디션 받으러
올지 모르겠다!
Maybe the monkey
will be at the audition.
안그래도 떨려 죽겠는데
겁주지마!
Don't make me more nervous
than I already am!
- 여러분, 안녕하세요?
- 커피 드릴까요?
- Good morning.
- Can I get you a cup of coffee, sir?
아뇨, 나도 여러분처럼
인턴 사원이에요
Oh, no, no. I'm an intern,
just like you guys.
넥타이에 서류가방을 들었고
차를 빌릴수 있는 나이이긴 하지만
Except for the tie, the briefcase
and the fact that I can rent a car.
정말이에요?
인턴 사원이라고요?
Seriously, you're an intern?
새로운 분야의 일을 해 보려고요
그럼 밑바닥부터 시작해야지요
I'm heading in a new career direction
and you gotta start at the bottom.
저런
Dude.
내가 나이는 좀 많지만
밥 호프 정도는 아니라구요
I know I'm a little older than you guys,
but it's not like I'm Bob Hope.
코미디언 몰라요?
USO?
The comedian. USO.
U.S.A. 인데요?
It's U.S.A., sir.
조이 트리비아니예요
이번 연극 제작진이에요
This is Joey Tribbiani.
Joey, these are the producers.
잘 알겠지만 이분은
레너드 헤이스 씨고요
And as you probably already
know, this is Leonard Hayes.
와! 만나뵙게 돼서 반갑습니다
선배님의 굉장한 팬이에요
It is so amazing to meet you.
I am such a big fan of your work.
내가 배역 운이 좋아서
좋은역을 많이 맡았지
I've been blessed with
a lot of great roles.
정말 대단하세요
"야간과 주말에는 무제한!"
Tell me about it, huh?
"Unlimited nights and weekends!"
날 놀리는 건가?
난 돈독 오른 사람이 아냐!
Are you making fun of me?
Because I am not a sellout.
돈 때문이 아니라 그 휴대폰
품질을 믿었기 때문에 한거야!
I didn't do it for money.
I believe in those phones!
질나쁜 무선통신 서비스 때문에
사촌을 잃을 뻔했다구!
I almost lost a cousin because
of bad wireless service.
절대로 놀린게 아닙니다
그 광고 정말 멋있어요
No, I wasn't making fun of you. I think
you were great in those commercials.
- 정말?
- 네
- Really?
- Yeah.
난 맡은 역은 확실하게
하는 편이거든
Well, I do bring a certain
credibility to the role.
맞아요! 선배님이
그 대포에서 발사 될때..
Are you kidding? When they shoot
you out of that cannon..
"그 전화 끊어요!"
"Hang up that phone!"
NG없이 한방에 찍었지
배역에 몰입했었지
- One take.
- Wow.
- 그럼 시작할까?
- 네, 좋습니다!
- So shall we read?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
2막 처음부터!
내가 등장하는 거야, 준비 됐지?
Top of Act 2. This is my entrance.
You got it?
아직까지 여기서 뭘하는 거지?
What the hell are you still doing here?
- 잘 알텐데!
- 나쁜 자식!
- I think you know.
- Bastard!
네가 그렇게 만들었어! 그거 아나?
난 당장이라도 갈수 있다!
I am what you made me.
You know what? I could go right now.
- 그럼 가버려!
- 갈수 없어!
- Go! Go!
- I can't.
가고는 싶지만, 긴 침묵
Oh, I want to, Long Pause..
갈수 없어!
but I can't.
이봐, "긴 침묵"은
대사가 아냐
So sorry. You're not supposed
to say "long pause."
아, 전 그게 선배님
역할 이름인줄 알았어요
Oh! Oh, I thought that was your
character's name. You know?
인디언 이름처럼 말예요
그런거 있잖아요
I thought you were, like, an Indian
or something, you know, with the..
아냐, 와줘서 고맙네
수고했어, 고맙네
No. Thank you so much for coming in.
We appreciate it. Thank you.
한번 더하면 안될까요?
You don't want me to do it again?
- 강약을 넣어서 해볼게요
- 됐어
- I could do an accent.
- No.
남부 사투리 어때요?
"당장이라도 갈수 있어!"
You know, Southern.
"l could go right now, mon!" Huh?
가관이군!
My God in heaven.
조이, 잠깐만요
레너드, 잠깐 얘기좀 할까요?
Joey, hang on. Leonard, can
we talk to you for a moment?
뭐? 농담하는 겁니까?
저 친구는 연기가 안돼요!
Yes? You've got to be kidding.
He can't act.
섹시하건 말건
상관없어요!
I don't care if you think he's hot.
저 친구와 자고 싶으면
개인적으로 해요! 이건 작품이야!
If you want to sleep with him,
do it on your own time. This is a play.
자꾸 이러면 당장
If you insist on this..
매니저에게 연락하겠어요!
I will call my agent so fast..
그 핸드폰으로! 음질이 선명해서
내가 옆방에 있다고 착각할걸?
on a cell phone connection so clear,
he's gonna think I'm next door!
절 위해 작은 소리로
얘기해 주셔서 고맙습니다
Hi, thank you so much for
whispering for my benefit.
제가 뭘 잘못했는지
말해줄수 없나요?
Tell me what I did wrong. I'd love to
work on it and try it again for you.
열심히 고치고 연습해서
다시 보여드리겠습니다
그리고.. 반가워요!
And also, how you doing?
한번만 더 기회를 주세요
잘 해보겠습니다!
Give me another chance.
I really want to get better. Please?
그럼 오늘 저녁 다시와
If you want to come back today..
- 그럼 잘듣게
- 네
- here are my notes. Ready?
- Yeah.
자넨 머리로 연기하고 있어!
생각이 너무 많아!
- You're in your head. Thinking too much.
- I really doubt that.
그럴리가 없는데요
아냐, 자네의 몸과 머리가
연결되지 않았어
No, no. It's that you're not
connected with anything in your body.
절박함이 없다구!
이 장면은 몸부림이란 말야!
There's no urgency.
The scene is a struggle.
경주같은 거라고
자네 연기는 수평적이었어
It's a race.
Also, what you did was horizontal.
과감하게 수직적인 방향으로
연기를 하란 말야
Don't be afraid to explore the vertical.
대사를 이해하려고 하지마
대사가 자네를 이해해야해
And don't learn the words.
Let the words learn you.
그냥 저 제작자 분과
잠자면 안될까요?
Couldn't I just sleep with the producer?
오늘 저녁 외식할래?
Hey, do you want to go
to dinner tonight?
안돼, 케이티라는 웨이트리스와
데이트 약속 있어
I can't. I've got a date
with that waitress, Katie.
지금까지 두번밖에
안만났지만
I know we've only gone out,
like, twice, but I don't know..
- 느낌이 아주 괜찮아
- 이혼을 알리는 종소리가 들리는군
- I have a good feeling about her.
- Oh, I hear divorce bells.
지갑 내놔!
그러면 조용히 보내주지!
Give me your wallets,
and there won't be a problem.
- 네?
- 난 총을 가지고 있어!
- What?
- I have a gun.
알았어요, 진정해요!
피비, 침착해!
Okay, relax, Phoebe.
Just stay calm.
어떡해!
지갑을 못찾겠어!
Oh, my God, I can't find my wallet!
- 이제 아가씨 지갑도 내놓으시지
- 싫어요
- All right, lady, now give me your purse.
- No.
싫다니 무슨 소리야!
너 때문에 나까지 죽어!
What do you mean "no"? I knew you'd
be my death, Phoebe Buffay!
- 혹시 로웰 아냐?
- 피비?
- Lowell, is that you?
- Phoebe?
- 이럴수가!
- 어쩜! 세상에!
- Oh, my God!
- Unbelievable! Oh, my God!
로스, 이쪽은
거리생활 할때 친구 로웰이야
I'm sorry. Ross, this is my old friend,
Lowell, from the streets!
- 로웰, 로스야
- 로스, 반가워요
- Lowell, Ross.
- Ross, nice to meet you.
네, 무척 반갑네요
Yeah, a real pleasure.
이게 얼마만이야!
정말 오랜만이네!
It's been so long! Oh, so long.
- 아직도 이짓 하는거야?
- 그렇게 됐어, 하지만 담배는 끊었어
- I can't believe you're still doing this.
- I know. But I quit smoking.
잘했네!
Good for you.
아주 좋아 보이는데?
You look like you're doing well.
옛날 삥 뜯던 시절의
때는 완전히 벗었는걸?
I guess your mugging days
are behind you.
맙소사! 피비!
너도 사람 돈 뺏었어?
Oh, my God.
Phoebe, you used to mug people?
로스, 잠깐만
옛친구와 할 얘기가 있거든
Excuse me, Ross,
old friends catching up.
- 오디션 어떻게 됐어?
- 오후에 다시 와보래
- How'd the audition go?
- They want to see me again, but..
그런데 레너드 헤이스가
날 안좋아해
Leonard Hayes did not like me.
- 무슨일 있었어?
- 나더러 절박하지가 않대
- What happened?
- He said I wasn't urgent enough.
내 연기는 수평적이었는데
수직적인 연기를 해야한대!
Everything I did was horizontal,
and I should be more vertical.
- 그리고 생각을 좀 덜하래!
- 그정도면 괜찮네
- He said that I should think less.
- Well, so far so good.
여보! 나 늙었어!
Honey, I'm old!
집에 와서
점심 먹는줄 몰랐네
I didn't know you were
coming home for lunch.
- 뭐줄까?
- 틀니 세척제 있어?
- Can I get you anything?
- Sure, a tube of Polident?
노인용 기저귀?
Some Depends?
100번째 생일 축하한다는
윌러드 스콧의 메시지
Birthday wishes from Willard Scott.
무슨일 있었어?
What's wrong?
다른 인턴 사원들에 비해
나 너무 늙었어, 경쟁이 안돼
I am so much older than these other
interns. I can't compete with them.
자기가 나이는 좀더 먹었지
So you're a little older.
하지만 긍정적으로 생각해
그만큼 인생경험이 많잖아
Look at the positive.
You have all this life experience.
그렇지만 인생경험이 이걸
해결하는데 도움이 될까?
Yes, but I don't think life experience
is gonna help me with these.
우와!
불타는것 같다!
Wow! It's like they're on fire!
- 저게 뭐야?
- 새로 나온 운동화 모델인데
- What are they?
- Prototype sneakers.
판매광고 아이디어를 짜야해
하지만 난 못해!
I need ideas on how to sell them.
Which I can't do..
생각이 있는 성인이라면
이런건 안신는다고!
because no self-respecting
adult would ever wear these.
500달러 줄께
이거 나 주라
I'll give you $500 for them.
이 난관을 어떻게 풀어야 하지?
- What am I supposed to do?
- Come on, sneakers are easy.
좋아, 우선 운동화는 편한거야
자기도 늘 운동화를 신잖아
- You wear them all the time.
- They're not called sneakers anymore.
우선, 이젠 아무도
운동화라는 말을 안써
"킥스", "스키즈"
"슬롭스"라고도 부르더군
They're called "kicks" or "skids."
I think I heard somebody say "slorps."
바퀴가 달려서 미끄러지기도 해
They've got wheels that pop out from
the bottom so you can roll around..
걷는게 너무 힘들어서 그랬나봐
because apparently
walking is too much exercise.
"어린이 여러분! 소아비만에
걸리려면 바퀴를 굴리세요!"
"Kids! Kids! Roll your
way to childhood obesity!"
요즘 애들은
살찌는 것도 쉽다니깐
Kids today have such
an easier time getting fat.
나 이것좀 팔게 도와줘!
Would you help me try to sell these?
가슴 빵빵한 여자를
이용해볼 생각 없어?
Okay. Have you considered
using a girl with huge knockers?
회사에서 원하는건
그런게 아닌것 같아
That's not what they're looking for.
난 그런 광고 좋은데!
Hey, that would work on me.
내가 버터워스 시럽을
사먹는 이유가 뭐겠어?
Why do you think I buy
Mrs. Butterworth's?
'센트럴
퍼크'
방금 우리가 무슨일
당했는지 알아?
You'll never guess what just happened.
- 피비랑 나, 강도 당했어!
- 다친데 없어?
- Phoebe and I got mugged!
- Are you okay?
피비랑 그 강도가
아는 사이더라구
Yeah. Phoebe knew the mugger.
강도를 어떻게 알아?
How do you know a mugger?
미안하지만 난 우리 여섯명 말고도
다른 친구들이 있어
I'm sorry, I have friends
outside the six of us.
어떻게 아는지 내가 말해줄까?
피비도 옛날에 사람 돈 뺐었대!
Know how she knew him?
Because Phoebe used to mug people.
정말이야?
Seriously?
떳떳한 일은 아니지만
Well, I'm not proud of it,
but, you know..
거리 생활할때 가끔 돈이나
먹을게 필요하면..
when I was living on the street and
I needed money for food and stuff..
- 피비, 너무 끔찍하다!
- 난 너희들처럼 부자가 아니었어!
- That is awful.
- I wasn't rich like you guys, okay?
밥 대신 금덩이를 먹지도 않았고
날개 달린 망아지도 없었어!
I didn't eat gold and have a flying pony.
어렵게 살았다구! 우리 엄마는
마약거래상한테 살해됐어
I had a hard life.
My mother was killed by a drug dealer.
- 엄마는 자살하셨잖아?
- 울엄마 마약거래상이었어
- Your mother killed herself.
- She was a drug dealer.
어쨌든 피비와 그 강도가 안면이
있기 망정이지 나 죽을 뻔했어!
It was a good thing she knew him.
I was about to do some serious damage.
아무렴
Okay.
오빠는 옛날의 나쁜 기억이
되살아났겠네
This must have brought back
some bad memories for you, Ross.
- 왜?
- 어렸을때 비슷한 일 당한적 있어
- Why?
- Ross was mugged as a kid.
- 그랬어?
- 그래, 정신적 충격이 아주 컸지
- You were?
- Yeah. And it was pretty traumatic.
세인트 마크 만화가게
앞에서였어
It was outside St. Mark's Comics.
이번주에는 스파이더 맨이
어떤 위험에 처했나 보고 있었지
I was minding my business, seeing what
kind of trouble Spider-Man was into.
원더우먼이었지!
Wonder Woman.
거기서 '누구'를 위해
Anyway, I was heading
towards this bakery..
빵 24개 사러
빵집 쪽으로 가고 있었는데
to pick up a couple of dozen
linzer tortes for someone..
갑자기 파이프를 든 불량배가
나타나서 말하는 거야
when out of nowhere, this thug
with a pipe jumps out and says:
- "돈 다 내놔, 꼬맹아!"
- 세상에!
- "Give me your money, punk!"
- Oh, my God.
끔찍했어! 제일 나빴던건 녀석이
내 배낭을 가져 간거야!
I know. And the worst part
was, they took my backpack..
내가 직접 그린 만화책
사이언스 보이가 들어있었거든!
which had all the original artwork I did
for my own comic book, Science Boy.
맞아!
걔는 어떤 초능력이 있었지?
Oh, yeah! What was
his super power again?
'지식에 대한 초인적인 열망'
A super-human thirst for knowledge.
강의하러 가야겠다
I better get to class.
내가 조심해야 할
네 친구들은 또 없니?
Are there any more of your
friends I should look out for?
제인 거리는 안가는게 좋을 거야
No. Actually, you might want to stay
away from Jane Street.
거긴 '칼잡이 조'의 구역이거든
That's where Stabby Joe works.
- 나 어떡하면 좋아!
- 왜?
- I think we have a problem here.
- What?
나 거리생활 할때 세인트 마크
만화가게가 내 구역이었어
Back in my mugging days,
I worked St. Mark's Comics.
- 그런데?
- 내 주무기가 파이프였고
- Yeah?
- A pipe was my weapon of choice..
10대 초반의 만화책 광들이
내 밥이었어
and preteen, comic-book nerds
were my meat.
그래서?
So?
그때 어떤 꼬마가 있었는데
그 배낭에 붙은 스티커에는..
There was one kid who had
a sticker on his backpack that said:
- "지질학 만세!"
- "Geology rocks!"
- 맙소사!
- 내가 로스 삥 뜯었어!
- Oh, my God!
- I know! I mugged Ross!
- 늦었군요
- 죄송해요!
- You're late.
- I know. I'm sorry.
그런데 잠깐
화장실에 다녀올게요
But can I just run to the bathroom?
안돼요, 레너드는
기다리지 않아요
- No. Leonard doesn't wait.
- But I am bursting with Yoo-hoo!
터지기 일보직전인데요
조이, 다시 왔군!
빨리 시작합시다
Joey, here we go!
Let's go. Very quickly.
- 실은 저..
- 시간없어, 빨리!
- I really need..
- We must go now, quickly.
- 예, 알겠습니다
- 준비됐나?
- Yeah. Yes, sir.
- Ready?
- 아직까지 여기서 뭘하는 거지?
- 잘 알텐데!
- What the hell are you still doing here?
- I think you know!
- 나쁜 자식!
- 네가 그렇게 만들었어! 그거 아나?
- Oh, you sick bastard!
- I am what you made me! Know what?
- 뭘!
- 난 당장이라도 갈수 있다!
- What?
- I could go right now.
- 그럼 가! 가버려!
- 갈수 없어!
- Then go. Go!
- Oh, I can't. I want to, but I can't!
가고는 싶지만 갈수 없어!
컷!
훌륭해!
Cut. That was good!
아주 좋았어!
내가 요구한걸 잘 소화했군
- Very good. You did everything I asked.
- I did?
그랬나요?
뭐라고 꼬집어 말할순 없지만
그 온몸을 비트는 연기
Yes. Plus which, you've got this,
I don't know, this squirmy quality..
내가 미처 생각하지 못한 캐릭터를
이끌어 냈어!
you bring to the character
I couldn't have imagined.
그렇게 하는거야!
Here's what we're gonna do:
내일 후원자들 앞에서
최종 오디션을 하겠네
Come back tomorrow
for the final callbacks.
오늘처럼 하는거야!
지금 그대로!
Do all of this, what you got
going now. But you know what?
하지만 좀더 강하게!
할수 있지?
More. More. Can you do that?
그럼요! 너무 급해서
감사인사는 나중에 할게요!
Sure. I don't have time to say
thank you because I really gotta go!
저것봐! 여전히 배역에 빠져있군!
정말 마음에 들어!
Look at that! Still in character.
I like him.
씨는 내가 뿌렸지만
정말 놀라운 일이야
I plant seeds. I can't explain it.
I don't know.
- 안녕, 뭐하는 거야?
- 그 운동화 신어 보는거야
- Hey. What are you doing?
- Putting on the sneakers..
좀더 젊은 감각을 가지면
영감이 떠오를것 같아서
to get in the young mindset,
see if it sparks anything.
- 뭐좀 떠올랐어?
- 이건 어때?
- Oh, anything yet?
- Yes, how's this?
"급소를 맞은듯한 짜릿한
불편함을 만끽하세요!"
"They're so uncomfortable, it's like
getting kicked in the nuts for your feet."
내가 왜이러는지
궁금하지?
You're probably wondering
what I'm doing.
너 늘 하던 짓이잖아
No, that seems about right.
어제 오디션 할때 화장실이 엄청
급하니까 좋은 연기가 나오더라구!
Yesterday at my audition, I had to pee.
Apparently, that makes me a good actor.
최종오디션 대비해서
마실거야, 참..
I got a callback, so I'm drinking
everything. Oh, by the way..
우리 냉장고 속에 있던
에그노그 죽이더라!
that eggnog in our fridge was great!
- 그거 엠마 우유였어
- 더 사다놓자!
- Joey, that was formula.
- We gotta get more of that.
이거 그리 나쁜건
아닌것 같아
These aren't half bad. You should
suggest these to Ralph Lauren.
이런거 랄프 로렌한테도
제안해보지 그래?
첫째, 너무 바보 같아
Okay, first of all, that's stupid.
Second, I'm not allowed to talk to Ralph.
둘째.. 나 회장님한테
말 못붙이게 돼있어
좋아!
벌써 젊어진 기분인걸?
All right. I feel younger already.
골반뼈 부러진것 같아!
Yeah, I think I broke my hip.
- 안녕, 로스!
- 안녕
- Hey, you!
- Hey.
강의 어땠어?
Hey. How was class?
아무도 그런거 물은적 없는데!
무슨 일이지?
No one asks me that. What's wrong?
- 그냥 궁금해서
- 오..
- Nothing. I really want to know.
- Oh.
글쎄.. 플라이스토세 지층에 대한
활발한 토론을 했어
Well, there was actually a rather lively
discussion about the Pleistocene..
좋아, 차라리 불고 말지
All right, nothing is worth this.
너한테 고백할게 있어
I have a confession to make.
어렸을때 네 가방 뺏었다던
그 여자애 말야
Okay, you know that girl that
mugged you when you were a kid?
무슨 소리야? 여자애 아냐
아주 덩치 큰 남자였어
What are you talking about?
It wasn't a girl. It was this huge dude.
갈퀴랑 창을 들고 있던 남자였어
He had a pitchfork and a sword.
더이상 거짓말 안해도 돼
그앤 14살짜리 여자 애였어
You don't have to lie anymore.
I know that it was a 14-year-old girl.
- 그렇지 않아
- 맞아
- No, it wasn't.
- Yes, it was.
아냐! 내가 아무렴 14살짜리
여자애 하나도 못 당했겠어?
You don't think I would have defended
myself against a 14-year-old..?
- 돈 다 내놔, 꼬맹아!
- 맙소사! 너였구나!
- "Give me your money, punk!"
- Oh, my God, it was you!
이럴수가!
네가 그 깡패였어?
I can't believe it. You mugged me?
정말 미안해, 로스
할말이 없어
Yeah. And I'm so, so sorry, Ross.
I'm sorry.
하지만 생각해보면
좋은것도 있어
But, you know, if you think
about it, it's kind of neat.
난 언제나 좀
따로 노는 기분이었거든
I mean, well, it's just that I've
always felt kind of like an outsider.
너희들 나머지는 모두
오래 전부터 알던 사이니까
You know, the rest of you have
connections that go way back..
이젠 너와 내가 공유할수 있는
어릴때 추억이 생긴거야
and, you know, now you
and I have a great one.
잊고싶은 기억이야!
It's not the best!
알아, 용서해줄래?
정말 할말이 없어
I know. Please forgive me.
I don't know what to say.
할말 없는게 당연하지!
내 평생 가장 창피한 일이었단 말야!
There's nothing you can say! That was
the most humiliating thing ever.
- 정말? 제일 창피한게..
- 됐어! 관둬!
- Even more humiliating than..
- Let's not do this!
그리고 광고 마지막에는..
욕조에서 여자들이 걸어나와
And then, at the end of the commercial,
the girls get out of the hot tub..
사랑을 나누기 시작하는 거예요
and start making
out with each other.
흥미롭군
That's interesting.
하지만 한마디하지
신발에 대해 전혀 언급이 없었어
Just one thought:
You didn't mention the shoes.
다음 사람?
챈들러?
Who's next? Chandler.
제 나이 또래의 남자가
You start with a guy
putting on the shoes.
- 이걸 신고 등장합니다
- 아저씨 또래요?
- He's about my age.
- Your age?
미끄러져 가다가 중심을 잃고
He's rolling down the street
and he starts to lose control.
쓰러져서 다치는 거예요
Maybe he falls.
Maybe he hurts himself.
그옆을 한 꼬마가 이걸신고
쏜살같이 달려갑니다
Just then, a kid comes flying
by wearing the shoes.
그리고 그 아저씨를 뛰어넘으며
웃는 겁니다, 그리고 자막이 나가죠
He jumps over the old guy and laughs.
And the line reads:
"어른들에겐 맞지 않아요!"
"Not suitable for adults."
- 챈들러, 아주 좋아요!
- 고맙습니다
- Well, Chandler, that's great.
- Thank you, sir.
저보다 두살 어리다죠?
Or, man who's two
years younger than me.
봤죠? 요점을
아주 잘 집어냈어요
You see, that has a clear selling point.
It appeals to our key demographic.
어린이층의 관심을
끌어내잖아요?
- 어떻게 생각해냈죠?
- 글쎄요, 모르겠어요!
- How did you come up with that?
- I don't know! I don't know!
젊은 감각을 가지려고
노력했더니 술술 나오더군요
I was just trying to get into a young
mindset, and stuff started to flow.
- 좋아요, 아주 잘했어요
- 고맙습니다
- That is great. Good work.
- Thank you.
내일 봅시다
We'll see all of you tomorrow.
날씨가 추우면
골반이 쑤셔서 말야
The cold weather hurts my hip.
안녕, 로스?
Hey, Ross. I know you're still mad at
me, but can I just talk to you for a sec?
나한테 아직 화가 나있겠지만
잠깐만 나랑 얘기좀 할래?
좋아, 말해
아, 미안! 좋아, 얘기해
Sure, go ahead. Oh, sorry.
Sure, go ahead.
진심으로 다시 사과할게
I just really wanted to apologize again.
그리고 네가 아주 좋아할 만한
물건을 가지고 왔어
And also show you something
I think you'll find very exciting.
'거리시절 잡동사니'
맙소사!
"거리시절 잡동사니"네!
Oh, my God! "Crap from the street!"
이안에는 뺏은 물건 중에
Look, Ross. In this box..
특별히 남겨뒀던게
들어있어, 팔거나
are all the things I got from mugging
that I thought were too special to sell..
태워버리지 않고 말이야
or smoke.
어쨌든 이 안에서 이게 나왔어
Anyway, I was looking
through it, and I found..
사이언스 보이!
Science Boy.
이럴수가!
Oh, my God!
이걸 다시보게 될줄은 몰랐어!
I never thought I'd see this again.
- 전부 다 있네!
- 그래
It's all here!
이걸 왜 지금까지
가지고 있었어?
What made you save
it all these years?
아주 훌륭하다고 생각했거든
I guess I just thought
it was really good.
언젠가 가치가 인정받는 날이
올거라고 생각했어
And maybe it would be
worth something one day.
정말 사이언스 보이가
소장할 가치가 있다고 생각했어?
You really thought Science Boy
was worth saving?
그래, 물론 이 안에는
바셀린 한통과
Yeah. But you should know I also have a
jar of Vaseline and a cat skull in here.
고양이 해골도
있다는걸 알아둬
어쨌든 굉장하다!
Still, this is amazing!
고마워, 피비
Oh, my God. Thank you, Phoebe.
천만에, 사이언스 보이 보게 해줘서
고마워, 많은걸 배웠어!
You're welcome. Thank you for
Science Boy. I learned a lot from him.
천만에
You're welcome.
잠깐만, 네가 뭘 더한거야?
Wait a minute.
Did you add something to him?
아, 그래
Oh, yeah.
주인공 남자를 그렇게 그리면
You see, the way you drew him..
'중력 걸'이 넘어올리가 없잖아
there was no way
he was ever gonna get Gravity Girl.
쫄바지 입은게
켄 인형 같더라
He looked like a Ken doll in those tights.
그게 뭐야?
뭐하는 거야?
What's that? What are you..?
"그거 비커니? 아니면
나보고 좋아서 그러니?"
"Is that a beaker
or are you happy to see me?"
이해가 안가
I don't get it.
- 대답을 듣고 싶어!
- 모르는데 어떻게 대답해!
- I need an answer!
- I can't tell you something I don't know.
- 알잖아!
- 난 몰라!
- You know!
- I don't know!
- 어서 대답하라니까!
- 좋아, 대답을 알고싶나? 대답은..
- I need an answer now!
- You want an answer? The answer is..
그녀는 날 사랑한적이 없어
너만을 사랑했다
She never loved me.
She only loved you.
그걸 알고도 지금까지 나한테
말을 안했어? 왜 말을 안했지?
You knew this all along
and you never told me?
널 용서하지 않을거야!
내 자신도 용서 못해!
I can never forgive you, or myself. I have
nothing to live for. Bang! And scene!
삶의 의미가 없어! 빵! 끝!
정말 완벽한 연기였어!
Absolutely amazing.
자네에게 역을 주겠네
- The part is yours.
- Thanks! Now I really gotta go.
감사합니다!
그럼 급해서 이만..
잠깐, 기다려!
축하하네! 결국 해냈군!
No, wait! Congratulations!
You did it.
해냈어!
이젠 긴장을 풀게
You did it. You can relax now. Yeah.
와, 케이블 TV요금이
왜 이렇게 많이 나왔지?
Wow! That's a big cable bill.
백수라도 포르노 보는데는
문제가 없나보지?
You don't have a job,
but you have no problem ordering porn.
토요일 오후?
On a Saturday afternoon?
나 집에 있을 때잖아!
I was in the house!
안녕
피비가 혹시 그 얘기..
Hey. Phoebe didn't by any
chance mention that..
오빠한테서 삥 뜯은 깡패가
피비였다는거? 들었어
She was the huge guy that
mugged you? Yeah.
설마 아무한테도..
I see. You didn't happen to tell..
아는 사람들한테
다 얘기했어
- Everybody we know? Yeah.
- Great. Thanks.
잘했어, 고마워